// data/flashcardsData.js
const flashcardsData = [
  {
    question: "Probably",
    answer: "Có lẽ",
  },
  {
    question: "Situation",
    answer: "Tình huống",
  },
  {
    question: "Energize",
    answer: "Tiếp thêm năng lượng",
  },
  {
    question: "Prefer",
    answer: "Thích hơn",
  },
  {
    question: "Routine",
    answer: "Lịch trình",
  },
  {
    question: "Clarification",
    answer: "Làm rõ",
  },
  {
    question: "Surgery",
    answer: "Ca phẫu thuật",
  },
  {
    question: "Contrast",
    answer: "Sự tương phản",
  },
  {
    question: "Latest",
    answer: "Mới nhất",
  },
  {
    question: "Variety",
    answer: "Đa dạng",
  },
  {
    question: "Concentrate",
    answer: "Tập trung",
  },
  {
    question: "Break",
    answer: "Phá vỡ",
  },
  {
    question: "Episode",
    answer: "Tập phim",
  },
  {
    question: "Daughter",
    answer: "Con gái",
  },
  {
    question: "Revision",
    answer: "Ôn tập",
  },
  {
    question: "Place",
    answer: "Địa điểm",
  },
  {
    question: "Nervous",
    answer: "Lo lắng",
  },
  {
    question: "Guide",
    answer: "Hướng dẫn",
  },
  {
    question: "Guide",
    answer: "Hướng dẫn",
  },
  {
    question: "Archive",
    answer: "Lưu trữ",
  },
  {
    question: "Trustworthy",
    answer: "Đáng tin cậy",
  }
];

export default flashcardsData;
